myccpay.com 2015-03-16

# Welcome to TCI Payments

**Privacy Policy Notice**

         Protecting the privacy and security of your personal information is a top priority for Total Card, Inc. This Privacy Policy Notice will help you understand how we safeguard and use information, and applies to all applicants, customers or former customers who obtain financial services from us for personal, family or household purposes. It also identifies the sources from which we collect non-public personal information about you, details the measures we take to secure that information, and describes the information about you that we may share with our affiliates and with nonaffiliated third parties. This Privacy Policy Notice also addresses information sharing with credit reporting agencies. This Privacy Policy Notice explains how you can exercise your privacy rights by electing to opt-out of certain information sharing practices that we would otherwise apply to your non-public personal information.

 **Collection of Personal Information.**

         We may collect personal information about you, which we believe to be necessary or useful in accurately and safely administering our business, and providing services, products and other opportunities to you. We collect non-public personal information about you from the following sources:

         • Information we receive from you on applications or other forms, such as your name, address, telephone number, date of birth, social security number, driver's license number, assets, and income;

         • Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others, such as your account balance, payment history, parties to transactions, and credit card usage; and

         • Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency, such as your credit worthiness and credit history.

         • We may use a software "cookie" when accessing our Online Banking product. No "cookie" will contain any information that would enable anyone to contact you via telephone, email or U.S. Mail. (A "cookie" is a small piece of information which a website stores in the web browser of your PC and can later retrieve. A "cookie" cannot be read by a website other than the one that set the "cookie". You can set your web browser to inform you when "cookies" are set to prevent "cookies" from being set.)

          **Disclosure of Personal Information.**

         We may disclose all of the information that we collect, as described above. We may disclose non-public information about you to the following types of third parties:

         • Financial service providers, such as mortgage bankers, securities broker - dealers, and insurance agencies;

         • Non-financial companies, such as retailers, direct marketers, airlines, and publishers; and 

         • Others, such as non-profit organizations.

         We may also disclose non-public personal information about you to non-affiliated third parties as permitted by law.

         We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf, or to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements.

         We do not knowingly solicit data from children, and we do not knowingly market to children. We recognize that protecting children's identities and privacy online is important and that the responsibility to do so rests with both the online industry and with parents.

          **Your Right to Opt-Out.**

         If you prefer that we not disclose non-public personal information about you to non-affiliated third parties, you may opt-out of those disclosures, that is, you may direct us not to make those disclosures (other than disclosures permitted by law). If you wish to opt-out of the disclosures to non-affiliated third parties, you may do so by completing the form included at the end of this notice and sending it to Correspondence Department, PO Box 90340, Sioux Falls, SD 57109.

          **Security Procedures.**

         We have safeguards to keep your non-public personal information confidential and secure. We restrict access to non-public personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your non-public personal information.

         We also deploy the following technologies to protect you:

         • We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) 128-bit encryption to encode and decode any information that is sent over the Internet between your computer and our server. Anyone “listening in” on the data transmission would hear only unintelligible gibberish.

         • Our server is located behind a firewall/router to prevent unauthorized people from being able to retrieve any applicant data stored there.

          **Additional Information Regarding Opt-Out Methods.**

         If you wish to tell us not to share your personal information with non-affiliated third parties and/or affiliates (except as permitted by law), please fill out the following form and mail it to the address stated thereon.

         We will treat an opt-out election by a customer with more than one account to apply to only the account(s) as listed on the form. The choices you make will remain in effect for the listed accounts until changed by you. It is not necessary to complete this form for any account for which you have previously submitted an opt-out form.

 **MARKETING OPT-OUT FORM**

         I have reviewed the privacy notice for each account or product noted, I am requesting that the sharing of personal information be limited as follows:

         Social Security No.: ______________________

         Check next to the appropriate statement or statements to indicate your preference(s)

Do not share information with non-affiliated third parties                     __________

Do not share information with affiliates (except as permitted by law)   __________

Name     _______________________________

Address _______________________________

             _______________________________

             _______________________________

Mail this form to:

Correspondence Department  
PO Box 89940  
Sioux Falls, SD 57109  
or call 800-536-6020

Privacy Policy Effective 02/08/2007.

Click here to print this page.
